Castle-Bache Collection 1683-1922 Mss.Film.1506
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1683-1922; 3 lin. feet
  - To Richard Bache, 1795 Mar. 30; Typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 Apr. 1; Orig. and typescript; Bache, William (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 May 13; Orig. and typescript; Bache, William (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 May 30; Orig. and typescript; Bache, William (Reel 3)
  - To William Bache, 1795 June 4; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Sarah and Richard (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 June 12; Markoe, William (Reel 3)
    Includes enclosure
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 June 14; Markoe, William (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 June 24; Robinson, Henry (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 June 25; Wolcot, John (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 July 2; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 3; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 3; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 3; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 July 4; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 5; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 8; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 10; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - Passport for William Bache, 1795 July 12; United States (Reel 3)
    Signed by James Mornoe, Minister to France
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 July 13; Orig. and typescript; Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 July 13; Typescript; Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 July 14; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 15; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 July 15; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 18; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 18; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 19; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1795 July 21; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 Aug. 5; Orig. and typescript; Harwood, John Edmund (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 Sept. 20; 3 Origs. and typescript; Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 Sept. 20; Transcript; Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 Sept. 24; Orig. and typescript; Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 Sept. 24; Orig. and typescript; Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 Dec. 9; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Sarah (Reel 3)
  - Notes of debates in Congress, 1795 Dec. 10-1796 Jan. 6; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 Dec. 12; Walker, John (Reel 3)
  - Notes of debates in Congress, 1795 Dec. 14-1796 May 23; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Jan. 6; Orig. and typescript; Bache, William (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Jan. 8; Typescript; Bache, William (Reel 3)
  - Notes of debates in Congress, 1796 Mar. 7-17; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - Notes of debates in Congress, 1796 Mar. 18-Apr. 10; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - Notes of debates in Congress, 1796 Apr. 15; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - Notes of debates in Congress, 1796 Apr. 27; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 July 26; Markoe, Peter, 1752?-1792 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Aug. 7; Orig. and typescript; Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Sept. 27; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Richard (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Sept. 27; Typescript; Bache, Richard (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Sept. 29; Markoe, Francis (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Sept. 30; Krause, William H. (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Oct. 22; Krause, William H. (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Nov. 13; 2 Cies, one enclosure; Krause, William H. (Reel 3)
  - To Charles Debrett, 1796 Dec. 3; Cy and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1796 Dec. 7; Krause, William H. (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1796 Autumn; Orig. and typescript; Tone, Matilda (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1796 Autumn; Orig. and typescript; Tone, Matilda (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1797 Jan. 8; Orig. and typescript; Markoe, Francis (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1797 Mar. 6; Orig. and typescript; Monroe, James, 1758-1831 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1797 Mar. 27; Markoe, Francis (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1797 May; Krause, William H. (Reel 3)
  - To George Fox, 1797 June 29; Franklin, William Temple (Reel 3)
  - To Richard Bache, 1797 July 15; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1797 July 24; 2 cies, enclosure; Krause, William H. (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1797 Oct. 8; Monroe, James, 1758-1831 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1797 Oct. 9; Orig. and typescript; Monroe, James, 1758-1831 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1797 Oct. 15; Orig. and typescript; Monroe, James, 1758-1831 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1797 Oct. 30; Orig. and typescript; Rowan, Archibald Hamilton (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1797 Nov. 21; Orig. and typescript; Monroe, James, 1758-1831 (Reel 3)
    With enclosures
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1798 Mar. 17; Orig. and typescript; Adams, Abigail (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1798 Mar. 26; Typescript; Monroe, James, 1758-1831 (Reel 3)
  - To a Subscriber in Washington, Pennsylvania, 1798 June 8; Cy and typescript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1798 June 25; Bache, Richard (Reel 3)
    With enclosure
  - To Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1798 July 14; Krause, William H. (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1798 Aug. 4; Orig. and typescript; Markoe, Francis (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1798 Aug. 4; Typescript; Markoe, Francis (Reel 3)
  - Will, 1798 Sept. 7; Cy, transcript; Bache, Benjamin Franklin, 1769-1798 (Reel 3)
  - Printed notice of death of Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1798 Sept. 11; Typescript (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1798 Nov. 9; Orig. and typescript; Prom, Elizabeth (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1798 Nov. 10; Orig. and typescript; Markoe, Francis (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1798 Nov. 12; Orig. and typescript; Snowden and McCorkle (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1798 Nov. 12; Typescript; Snowden and McCorkle (Reel 3)
  - Letter of administration for estate of Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1798 Nov. 19; Campbell, George (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1798 Dec. 2; Orig. and typescript; Eustace, I. S. (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1798 Dec. 2; Typescript; Eustace, I. S. (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1799 Jan. 12; Orig. and typescript; Aurora. Compositors and Pressmen (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1799 Jan. 15; Orig. and typescript; Aurora. Compositors and Pressmen (Reel 3)
  - To the Aurora. Compositors and Pressmen, 1799 Jan. 15; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1799 May 17; Orig. and typescript; Markoe, Francis (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1799 Nov. 2; Orig. and typescript; Dallas, Alexander James, 1759-1817 (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Bache, 1799 Nov. 2; Orig. and typescript; Dallas, Alexander James, 1759-1817 (Reel 3)
  - To Alexander James Dallas, 1799 Nov. 4; Cy and typescript; Bache, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To the Aurora. Compositors and Pressmen, 1799; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To George Fox, 1800 July 3; Franklin, William Temple (Reel 3)
  - To Alexander James Dallas, 1800 Sept. 22; Markoe, Francis (Reel 3)
  - To William Duane, 1800 Nov. 25; Orig. and typescript; Dawson, John (Reel 3)
  - To Sarah Bache, 1801 Mar. 12; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Deborah (Reel 3)
  - To Richard Bache, 1801 May 13; Cy and transcript; Bache, Sarah (Reel 3)
  - To William Duane, 1802 Jan. 14; Wolcot, John (Reel 3)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1804 Mar. 8; Duane, William (Reel 3)
  - Certificate for one share, 1804 Sept. 3; Company for Promoting the Cultivation of the Vine in Pennsylvania (Reel 3)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1805 Feb. 28; Duane, William (Reel 3)
  - To the Tribunal of the Guardians of St. Croix, 1805 Dec. 2; Cy; Duane, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Duane, 1806 Feb. 11; Heyleger, Isaac (Reel 3)
  - To Peter Markoe, 1807 Mar. 10; Cy; Duane, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Duane, 1807 June 20; Markoe, Peter, 1752?-1792 (Reel 3)
  - To Joseph Clay, 1807 June 25; Markoe, Peter, 1752?-1792 (Reel 3)
  - To Peter Markoe, 1808 Oct. 10; Cy; Duane, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Duane, 1808 Dec. 24; 2 Cies, enclosure; Markoe, Peter, 1752?-1792 (Reel 3)
  - To Sarah Bache, 1808 Dec. 29; Franklin, William (Reel 3)
  - To Peter Markoe, 1809 Apr. 1; Cy; Duane, Margaret Hartman (Reel 3)
  - To Richard Bache, 1809 Apr. 6; Franklin, William (Reel 3)
  - To George Fox, 1809 July 3; Franklin, William Temple (Reel 3)
  - Valedictory oration at the Commencement of the University of Pennsylvania, 1810 June 1; Orig. and typescript; Bache, Franklin (Reel 3)
  - To Margaret Hartman Duane, 1810 June 24; Markoe, Peter, 1752?-1792 (Reel 3)
  - Will, 1813 Apr. 15; Typescript; Franklin, William (Reel 3)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1813 May 17; United States. Army. Infantry Regiment, 32nd (Reel 3)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1814 Feb. 25; Duane, William (Reel 3)
  - To William Duane, 1814 Mar. 29; Dorsey, John S. (Reel 3)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1814 Apr. 11; Dorsey, John S. (Reel 3)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1814 July 7; Duane, William (Reel 4)
  - Will, 1814 Oct. 24; Cy; Franklin, William Temple (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1815 Feb. 15; Cy and typescript; Duane, Margaret Hoffman (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1815 Mar. 1; Duane, Margaret Hoffman (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1815 Mar. 2; Duane, Margaret Hoffman (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1816 May 24; United States. Army. Superintendant General (Reel 4)
  - General Order, 1816 June 24; United States. Army. Inspector General (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1816 Aug. 24; Philadelphia Dispensary. (Reel 4)
  - To Hartman Kuhn, 1817 June 6; Duane, Margaret Hoffman (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1818 Jan. 21; Philadelphia Dispensary. (Reel 4)
  - Orders, 1818 Mar. 28; United States. Army. Military Department, 4th. Headquarters (Reel 4)
  - To Margaret Hartman Duane, 1818 May 16; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1820 Aug. 1; Rowan, Sally (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1820 Aug.; Duane, William (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1820 Aug.; Duane, William (Reel 4)
  - To William Duane, 1820 Nov. 9; 2 Cies; Markoe, Peter, 1752?-1792 (Reel 4)
  - Will, 1821 Jan. 21; Cy; Bache, Catherine Wistar, 1770-1820 (Reel 4)
  - To William Duane, 1821 Dec. 23; Markoe, Peter, 1752?-1792 (Reel 4)
  - To George Fox, 1823 July 30; Cy; Franklin, Hannah (Reel 4)
    Includes George Fox to Hannah Franklin
  - To George Fox, 1823 Aug. 9; Co.; Harris, Farquhart and Co. (Reel 4)
    With enclosure and George Fox to Harris, Farquhart and Co.
  - To Aglae Dabadie Bache, 1823 Aug. 20; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To George Fox, 1823 Oct. 28; Bayard, William (Reel 4)
  - To George Fox, 1823 Nov. 1; Orig. and typescript; Hanbury, Capel Sampson (Reel 4)
  - To George Fox, 1823 Dec. 4; Collier, Hannah (Reel 4)
  - To George Fox, 1824 Mar. 31; Harris, Farquhart and Co. (Reel 4)
  - To Aglae Dabadie Bache, 1824 May 27; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Aglae Dabadie Bache, 1824 June 1; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Aglae Dabadie Bache, 1824 July 27; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To George Fox, 1824 Aug. 24; Franklin, Hannah (Reel 4)
  - To George Fox, 1824 Nov. 23; Hanbury, Capel Sampson (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1825 Jan. 11; Duane, William (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1825 Apr.; Duane, William (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1825 July 18; Duane, William (Reel 4)
  - Copy of invoices, accounts, and orders of John Dabadie, 1818-1825 (Reel 4)
  - To Elizabeth Duane, 1826 May 28; Duane, William (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1826 Sept. 7 (Reel 4)
  - To the Franklin Institute, 1826 Sept. 8; Cy; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1826 Dec. 19; Warren, John Collins (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1827 Jan. 15; Bache, Richard (Reel 4)
  - To John Collins Warren, 1827 Jan. 27; ADf; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - Will, 1827 Apr. 30; Cy; Duane, Margaret Hartman (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1827 Aug. 16; Aavestrup, Charles William (Reel 4)
  - To Frederica Dabadie, 1827 Nov. 9; Bache, Aglae Dabadie, 1796-1835 (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1828 Jan.; Hays, Isaac (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1828 Mar. 14 (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Institute, 1828 Mar. 15; Cy; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1828 July 28; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Aglae Dabadie Bache, 1830 Jan. 1; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Aglae Dabadie Bache, 1830 Jan. 3; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Aglae Dabadie Bache, 1830 June 9; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Aglae Dabadie Bache, 1830 June 11; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Aglae Dabadie Bache, Caroline Bache, and Margaret Bache, 1830 June 16; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Mrs. James P. Boyd, 1830 July 17; Cy; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1830 Nov. 24; Markoe, Francis (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1830 Dec. 6; Markoe, Francis (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1830 Dec. 9; Markoe, Francis (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1830 Dec. 10; Markoe, Francis (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1831 Mar. 7; Wright, James (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1831 Apr. 25; Markoe, Francis (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1831 May 25; Philadelphia College of Pharmacy (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1831 Sept. 28; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1831 Oct. 10; Markoe, Sally (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1832 Apr. 13; Markoe, Sally (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1832 Apr. 28; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1832 May 18; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1832 July 16 (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1832 Oct. 30; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1833 Jan. 4; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1833 July 17; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1833 Sept. 9; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1833 Sept. 30; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1833 Oct. 4; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1833 Oct. 29; Boyd, James McHenry (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1833 Nov. 2; Boyd, James McHenry (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1833 Nov. 6; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1834 Mar. 27; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1834 Apr. 5; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1834 Sept. 3; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1834 Sept. 10; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1836 Jan. 12; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1836 Jan. 13; Markoe, Francis (Reel 4)
  - To Richard Barnes Mason, 1836 Jan. 13; Scott, Winfield (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1836 Apr. 7; Markoe, Francis (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1836 Apr. 13; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Levi Woodbury, 1836 Apr. 23; Clay, Joseph A. (Reel 4)
  - To James Bayard, 1836 May 25; United States. Treasury Dept. (Reel 4)
  - To James Bayard, 1836 June 20; Woodbury, Levi (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1836 July 29; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - Deposition to the Circuit Court, Washington, D.C., 1836?; Cy; Frevall, Peter E. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1837 Jan. 7; Eastern State Penitentiary. Board of Inspectors (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1837 Jan. 13; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1837 Jan. 19; Markoe, Francis (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1837 Feb. 20; Eastern State Penitentiary. Board of Inspectors (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1837 Apr. 13; Rowan, Sally (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1837 Nov. 12; Rowan, Sally (Reel 4)
  - To James Bayard, 1838 July 5; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1840 Jan. 30; Woodbury, James (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1840 Feb. 1; United States. Mint (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1840 Feb. 24; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1840 June 25; Sparks, Jared (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1840 July 2; Philomathean Society (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1840 Sept. 23; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1841 Apr. 6; Jefferson Medical College. (Reel 4)
  - To James Bayard, 1841 May 30; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1841 June 21; Philadelphia College of Pharmacy (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1841 June 24; Philadelphia College of Pharmacy (Reel 4)
  - Settlement of John Dabadie's estate, 1841 Dec. 9; Bache, Franklin (Administrator) (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1842 Feb. 2; Markoe, Francis (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1845 Aug. 31; Bache, Charles Meigs and Albert Dabadie Bache (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1848 Feb. 18; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1850 June 12; Bowdith, William J. (Reel 4)
  - Miscellaneous notes of a visit to France, 1851 Nov. 7; Bache, Thomas Hewson (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1851 Aug. 5; Stevens, Henry (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1852 May 8; Dreyfose (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1853 Feb. 25; Jefferson Medical College. Committee (Reel 4)
  - To Jefferson Medical College. Committee, 1853 Feb. 25; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Societies and individuals in correspondence with the APS, 1853 Apr. 8; American Philosophical Society. (Reel 4)
  - To Societies and individuals in correspondence with the APS, 1853 Apr. 14; American Philosophical Society. (Reel 4)
  - Diary, 1853 Apr. 16-Nov. 4; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1854 Feb. 3; Imperial Society of Naturalists (Moscow, Russia) (Reel 4)
  - To the Imperial Society of Naturalists (Moscow, Russia), 1854 Apr. 4; Bache, Franklin (Reel 4)
  - To Albert Dabadie Bache, 1854 Aug. 7; Sumber, Eliza P. (Reel 4)
    With enclosure: Thomas W. Sumner Memorandum of the portrait of Dr. Benjamin Franklin (Cy)
  - To Moses Thomas, 1855 Mar. 3; [Duffield]?, Alfred (Reel 4)
    Enclosure
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1855 Apr. 20; Motley, Thomas (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1855 Apr. 24; Greene, Lydia (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1856 Mar. 10; Dohrn, Karl A. (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1856 May 7; Motley, Thomas (Reel 4)
  - To Henry Stevens, 1856 Sept. 8; Cy; Bache, Thomas Hewson (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1856 Sept. 30; [Duffield]?, Alfred (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1856 Oct. 17; Stevens, Henry (Reel 4)
  - To Richard Meade Bache, 1857 Apr. 6; Bache, Charles Meigs, 1829-1890 (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1857 Sept. 22; American Pharmaceutical Society (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1857 Oct. 5; Peale, Rembrandt, 1778-1860 (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1858 Mar. 25; Darlington, William, 1782-1863 (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1859 Apr. 8; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1859 Apr. 13; Whithead, A. (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1859 Apr. 21; Markoe, Franics, Jr. (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1859 May 3; Motley, Thomas (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1859 Aug. 5; Hutchinson, Charles H. (Reel 4)
  - To Henry Jackson, 1860 Sept. 11; Cy; Watson, John Fanning (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1860 Nov. 21; Jackson, Henry (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1860 Dec. 19; Jackson, Henry (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1863 Jan. 21; Pennsylvania Institution for the Deaf and Dumb (Reel 4)
  - To Franklin Bache, 1863 Jan. 24; Pennsylvania Institution for the Deaf and Dumb (Reel 4)
  - To Alexander Dallas Bache, 1864 Mar. 24; Hughes, William and John N. Trook (Reel 4)
  - To William Hughes and John N. Trook, 1864 Mar. 24; Cy; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867 (Reel 4)
  - To United States. Surgeon General, 1864 Mar. 27; Cy; Baltimore (Md.). Medical Director (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1864 June 21; Baylies, Henry (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1864 June 26; McAllister, John A. (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1864 July 17; McAllister, John A. (Reel 4)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1864 July 26; Baylies, Henry (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1864 July 31; McAllister, John A. (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1864 Sept.; McAllister, John A. (Reel 5)
  - Military pass, 1864 Dec. 17; Bache, Charles Meigs, 1829-1890 (Reel 5)
  - Military pass, 1865 Apr. 25; Bache, Charles Meigs, 1829-1890 (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1866 Aug. 20; Sergeant, J. Dickinson (Reel 5)
  - To Levi Groff, 1866 Nov. 26-29; Bache, Thomas Hewson (Reel 5)
    Includes A. B. Groff to Thomas Hewson Bache, enclosures
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1867 Mar. 2; New York (State). Chamber of Commerce (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1868 Aug. 4; Rowan, Sally (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1868 Dec. 11; Hunt, Ezra M. (Reel 5)
  - Minutes of the meeting, 1871 Mar. 15; Journal Association of the College of Physicians of Philadelphia (Reel 5)
  - Minutes (extract), 1872; Cy; New England Historic Genealogic Society (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1873 Apr. 22; Duane, Richard B. (Reel 5)
  - Passport for Thomas Hewson Bache, 1874 Jan. 3; United States (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1875 June 4; Waugh, Samuel B. (Reel 5)
  - To George W. Cadwalader, 1875 Dec. 4; Cy; Stetson, Charles Augustus, 1810-1888 (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1876 Jan. 9; Coxe, Brinton (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1876 May 12; McAllister, James W. (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1876 June 22; Waugh, Samuel B. (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1876 June 23; Tradesmen's National Bank (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1876 July 10; White, E. R. (Reel 5)
  - To James L. Clagham, 1876 Nov. 17; Russell, Samuel H. (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1877 Feb. 2; American Philosophical Society. (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1877 Feb. 27; Russell, Samuel H. (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1877 Mar. 10; Etter, David (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1877 Mar. 16; Darley, Francis Sully (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1877 Mar. 20; Cohill, Charles (Reel 5)
  - To Alexander Dallas Bache, 1877 Mar. 23; Totten, Catlyna (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1877 Apr. 30; Rowan, Sally (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1877 Oct. 30; Hutchinson, Charles R. (Reel 5)
  - New York Times. Editor, 1879 June 29; C.H.H. (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1879 Sept. 17; McAllister, John A. (Reel 5)
  - To Thomas Hewson Bache, 1879 Nov. 21; Heard, J. Theo (Reel 5)